(Episode 101) You just leave after sex with me.
You don't acknowledge me when you're done, huh?
Isn't this what I learned from you?
Why didn't you tell me about your return?
You already have a new love.
Why should I tell you?
I have a new love?
What?
Your new love is waiting for you.
Scarlett.
What a coincidence to see you two.
Oh, Miss Hall, don't misunderstand.
I just happened to meet Mr. Bradley.
We're not in that relationship.
It's alright, he and I are just cousins.
Niko, didn't you say that you were waiting
for my cousin-in-law to remarry you?
What?
Cousin?
You and...
Scarlett really is my cousin.
But I saw it in the news that...
Entertainment news is all lies.
I was doing fashion shows in France before.
I just returned to the country and have no
resources,
so I begged my cousin
for some help.
Just because you read some entertainment news,
you believe that there is something going on
between Scarlett and me?
Ah,
Noemi, you
take entertainment news seriously?
No wonder you were hostile to me last night.
Noemi,
you just don't trust me, do you?
I didn't mean to.
Besides, you didn't trust me before.
Well, I'll leave you guys alone.
The first time I met your cousin,
I embarrassed myself like this.
Niko,
I won't be able to face anyone in the future.
I'll take you home
and hide you away.
So you won't have to see anyone anymore.
Are you trying to keep me captive?
I want to treasure you.
Hmph.